// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "PowerPoint is best described as _______.",
    answer: "C. Presentation software",
    options: [
      "A. Database software",
      "B. Editing Software",
      "C. Presentation software",
      "D. Outlook software"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "How can you add video?",
    answer: "D. Click insert > video then choose if Online View or Video on my PC > choose video folder > insert",
    options: [
      "A. Click insert > choose in video folder > insert",
      "B. Right click > video and choose locate folder then press okay",
      "C. Click insert > video then choose if Online View or Video on my PC > choose video folder > Okay",
      "D. Click insert > video then choose if Online View or Video on my PC > choose video folder > insert"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Juan wants to link slide 1 to slide 3, what action will he do?",
    answer: "D. Right click > link > place in this document",
    options: [
      "A. Right click > hyperlink > place this link",
      "B. Right click > link > place this hyperlink",
      "C. Right click > link > create new document",
      "D. Right click > link > place in this document"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What specific application allows you to create slide presentations for a lecture or topic that motivates and persuades the audience?",
    answer: "B. Presentation",
    options: [
      "A. Outlook",
      "B. Presentation",
      "C. Spreadsheet",
      "D. Word"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following buttons will you click to insert an image?",
    answer: "C. Pictures",
    options: [
      "A. Audio",
      "B. Online View",
      "C. Pictures",
      "D. Videos"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Rey wants to start his slideshow using the keyboard. What function does he need to press?",
    answer: "D. F5",
    options: [
      "A. Ctrl+P",
      "B. Ctrl+S",
      "C. F1",
      "D. F5"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "When updating the link, you need to right-click on the link then click ___.",
    answer: "B. Edit Link",
    options: [
      "A. Ctrl +E",
      "B. Edit Link",
      "C. Link",
      "D. Edit this document"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "To resize the picture and video, click and _____ the corner handle.",
    answer: "C. Drag",
    options: [
      "A. Enter",
      "B. Escape",
      "C. Drag",
      "D. Save"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is the main purpose of PowerPoint?",
    answer: "D. To create Presentation",
    options: [
      "A. To create videos",
      "B. To create pictures",
      "C. To create documents",
      "D. To create Presentation"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is the shortcut key to press if you want to end the presentation?",
    answer: "A. Esc",
    options: [
      "A. Esc",
      "B. Enter Tab",
      "C. Tab",
      "D. Shift"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "What is the first layout of the slide you will choose if you want to create a presentation?",
    answer: "C. Title slide layout",
    options: [
      "A. Blank layout",
      "B. Title only layout",
      "C. Title slide layout",
      "D. Title and content layout"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "What is the first step in hyperlinking?",
    answer: "C. Highlight the text and press right click then link.",
    options: [
      "A. Save presentation",
      "B. Add another slide for the hyperlink",
      "C. Highlight the text and press right click then link.",
      "D. Use images, text, URL, or shapes when hyperlinking."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Which of the following statements below describe the function of the playback tab?",
    answer: "D. It provides options on how the movie will be played and displayed during the slideshow",
    options: [
      "A. It gives false information about your video",
      "B. The slideshow will end after clicking insert",
      "C. The slideshow will start after clicking playback",
      "D. It provides options on how the movie will be played and displayed during the slideshow"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "To adjust or edit the picture in the slide, press right-click then select ______.",
    answer: "C. Format picture",
    options: [
      "A. Pictures",
      "B. Change position",
      "C. Format picture",
      "D. Change picture"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Which of the following is NOT true about a PowerPoint presentation?",
    answer: "C. It can be boring because of verbose rather than graphics",
    options: [
      "A. It becomes more interesting to the audience",
      "B. It allows using images, videos, audio, and animation",
      "C. It can be boring because of verbose rather than graphics",
      "D. It helps the presenter to catch the attention of the audience"
    ]
  },
];
